[Music]
finding the right Talent with the right
skill sets whether both technical or
even on the business side has always
been a struggle for us to grow and
ultimately to serve our clients we're
also competing you know in the same area
we try to search for the same candidate
you can't just keep hiring from other
partners well we'll need new talent
because the market is growing A New
Perspective and Millennials and younger
people are bringing that perspective
that's where the res skill program came
in the first emotion was just pure
excitement because if Microsoft comes
with a new initiative and you want to
jump on the wagon and it aligned with
the kind of consultant we're trying to
develop I thought that uh changing
Fields was going to be a really long and
hard task when we start the program
everything was starting to make sense
and now we're just having fun with it
this is a great program with great
people great skills and it will help me
be the best in my career that I can
possibly be the fact that res skill is
combining both the recruiting and the
training and onboarding and mentoring of
those candidates is a huge advantage and
a great value after 12 weeks they
started being billable which is a very
big Advantage for us as a company is
definitely paying off it would be much
more expensive if we had to do all of
this ourselves this is finally what
we've beening looking for a way where
Microsoft as the publisher was
partnering with us to try to find that
next Generation talent pool that we
really need to bring into the ecosystem
the future is business Central the time
to switch is now and the res skill
program has been a great help for me if
you're a partner this is a no-brainer
why not why not
[Music]